starstore.com 2011-10-05

# Privacy Policy

• Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).  
• Any information that you supply to us is only used for the purpose for which you originally supplied it (e.g. despatching your order).   
• We do not share or sell or otherwise exchange your email or other personal or contact details with any other companies or organisations.   
• We do use cookies to track aggregate user information (to help us improve this site) and to implement certain features on this site like the shopping basket and checkout.   
• We may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our web pages. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party websites. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad network Web site, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as if you had requested a web page from our website.

**About Us**  
This is the web site of starstore.com and is owned by The Last Picture Show. Our postal address is:   
The Last Picture Show  
38 – 39 The Lanes  
Meadowhall Centre   
Sheffield S9 1EP  
United Kingdom  
We can be reached via e-mail at shop@starstore.com or by phone on 0114 2569604 (UK) / 0044 114 2569604 (outside UK) 

**The Information We Collect**  
We collect visitor information on an aggregate basis to use to monitor and improve this site. For example, we keep a record of the pages downloaded from our site (as all web servers do). We do not share this information with anyone else.  
We store the personal details you enter when buying goods. We use this information to process and deliver your order. We do not share this information with anyone else except for delivery requirements when we employ third parties, couriers to make deliveries and Royal Mail to send post. We may provide your telephone number to a courier should they need to contact you regarding your delivery.

If you choose to pay by credit or debit card, you will be asked to provide your card details on a secure form using 128-bit encryption. We only store credit card information while we need it to process an order - and then delete it from our system. Credit card details are not shared with anyone other than the card holders issuing bank or the authorised secure processor to obtain credit card authorisation. Credit card details are not held on the web site, and the customer has to re-enter for every transaction.

For our News Letter, we collect and store the email address you enter when you sign-up. We do not share this information with anyone else. When placing an order, we will send the visitor e-mails directly relating to the registration or order. You may opt in to our mailing list by ticking the ‘remember me’ option on the Order form. We may additionally send one e-mail to the customer inviting them to opt in to the mailing list. Customers may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time.

We may use your information to administer any prize draws or competitions you may enter.

We may use your personal information in the prevention and detection of fraud.  
We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties. If we choose to do so in the future, you will be notified by email of our intentions, and have the right to be removed prior to the disclosure.

By using our website you consent to the collection and use of this information by us.   
**  
Cookies**  
This site uses cookies for the purposes described above.   
**  
Security**  
We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving personal and financial consumer information.   
**  
Links**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.  
**  
Checking Your Information**  
Upon request we will provide site visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them. A charge may be levied, to cover our processing costs. Proof of identity is required for such information.   
Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us an e-mail at shop@starstore.com   
**  
Any Questions**  
If you have any questions or require clarification, please contact us at shop@starstore.com
